= kissasia.co =
SAY NO TO PIRACY, SUPPORT ORIGINALS
ADAPTED FROM THE EARLY SPRING ON JJWXC.NET
AUTHOR: GU NIANG BIE KU
You got one word wrong. Retype everything.
Your father scolded you back then.
You got angry and broke the typewriter.
Although your father hit you with a ruler,
he still fixed the typewriter
until three in the morning.
He even had me lie to you
and say the nanny fixed it.
THE FIRST PERSON
TO FALL IN LOVE WILL LOSE EVERYTHING
Mr. Luan, you've lost it.
I just want to keep
a professional distance between us.
She can control it.
Why would I lose control?
All right. You didn't lose control.
Oh. I bought a new car.
Help me claim it as expenses.
LIME SUPPLIER DATABASE - EVENT COMPANIES
LIME SUPPLIER DATABASE - PHOTOGRAPHY TEAM
LIME SUPPLIER DATABASE - MEDIA COMPANY
Have you verified the data in this column?
Have a piece of cake first.
Let me help you amend it.
Tao.
Listen to me.
Lowering your boss's expectations
appropriately is also a life hack.
Don't back yourself into a corner.
Lower it more?
I'm already worthless,
and I still have to lower it?
He'll just fire me.
I heard a very important figure
sent you back tonight.
Have you had a new breakthrough?
What are you talking about?
I'm just a rookie
who just stepped out of the tutorial.
I've faced a max-level boss.
An ultimate move from him,
and I'd have died multiple times.
Don't talk nonsense.
Encountering troubles at work is common.
I'll work a bit
to help you out this weekend.
Really?
Thank you.
Tao, I'm worried about you now.
How long can you last walking a tightrope
between your work performance
and your feelings?
Our instructor told us
to maintain a safe distance
if we didn't want to collide
with the car in front.
Your instructor is right.
But did he tell you this?
If you encountered a steep corner,
you panicked and stepped on the gas pedal,
you wouldn't be able to control
whether the car would flip over or not.
It's dangerous. It's too dangerous.
The board has made a decision.
Mr. Lin will be transferred
to the United States.
He wanted me
to win Yueteng back this quickly
because he wanted to go
to the headquarters to give a job report.
Can you focus on yourself?
I heard your appointment
as the interim general manager
will become official soon.
You just heard about it.
Let me know when it is official.
Don't tell me
that you're not interested in a promotion.
You need to handle
the Yueteng project well.
Do it steadily.
Don't cause any unnecessary trouble.
For example, doing some kind
of supplier grading scheme.
Breaking the long-standing custom
means affecting
other people's slice of the pie.
What?
Someone even made complaints to you?
That means my decision is working.
A long-standing custom
doesn't mean it's a good cycle.
What you need to do
is find talents that the company can use.
What I need to do is prevent
financial losses for the company.
LIME SUPPLIER EVALUATION TABLE
Judging from your expression,
is there some kind of good news?
The employee you hired is quite capable
when it comes to execution.
She made something impossible happen.
We'll separate suppliers
into three categories.
Event companies, photography teams,
and media channels.
We will visit these suppliers
and give them a grade
based on various factors.
Take event companies, for example.
We'll rate them in terms of past events,
brand expertise, and cooperation levels.
SUPPLIER RATINGS BASED ON VARIOUS FACTORS
THANK YOU FOR YOUR TIME
We'll continue to refine the details.
Coming here is worth it today.
Your proposal is efficient,
simple, and innovative.
It has completely exceeded
our expectations.
The most impressive thing about it
is that you've compiled
such a systematic supplier database
for our project.
The standard of Lime is indeed impressive.
You're right.
Before I came here,
WAN JUN, YUETENG'S REPRESENTATIVE
I heard Mr. Luan from Lime
has the "Hand of God."
I've finally known
the meaning of the phrase
"speed is the essence of war" today.
I'm impressed.
I'm not the only one in Lime.
There are also many outstanding employees.
The prototype of this database
you see here
was spearheaded by Flora,
who recently joined the team.
Mr. Luan, not only are you capable,
but your management skills
are also top-notch.
Since we have a strong
supplier database to back us up,
the annual framework
that we talked about previously
can also proceed.
Great.
I'll get the legal department
to draft a contract right away.
Right, Luke?
You can arrange it.
Thank you very much.
To a great partnership.
- Thank you.
- To a great partnership.
Take care.
As expected of you, Luke.
You got the client successfully.
Flora, you've also been outstanding today.
You completed the initial phase
of the supplier database alone.
It's not something you can do
with just a few clicks of the mouse.
It requires strong logical thinking
and data analysis skills.
Not bad.
You are quite the talent.
My boss taught me well,
and my colleagues helped me a lot.
Does the HRBP only praise people
without giving any actual reward?
No need. It's what I should do.
Why not?
Do you not want to become
a senior account executive?
It's possible for you to become an SAE.
However, the company policy states
that you need the signature
and recommendation from your superior.
Do you want Luke or Alex
to be your referrer?
I'll go with the boss's decision.
‪Tracy.
I see.
Luke, let's talk in the office.
Sure.
There's a very tricky problem now.
What is it?
How should we celebrate this?
Anything is fine.
I thought today's meeting
was interesting enough.
I didn't expect to see
something even more interesting.
LIME'S SENIOR EXECUTIVE
FOOLS AROUND WITH MULTIPLE WOMEN
MISTREATING HIS EX, CAUSING HER
TO COMMIT SUICIDE, ACCUSED PARTY: LUKE
These are obviously photoshopped.
I don't have this weird habit.
Moreover, my body is in better shape.
Mr. Luan, can't you see the objective
of slandering you using your private life
at a time like this?
Who received this besides you?
I asked our colleagues at the IT division
to run a check.
30% of our colleagues
received it, at least.
They include all senior executives.
Tell me. How do you plan to settle this?
Find three of my exes
and send them a few emails
to prove that this isn't me.
If you don't settle this properly,
I'll have no choice but to get help
from the internal audit and legal teams.
I agree.
Draft an email as soon as possible
and send it to the board.
Request the group
to send down an investigation unit
to investigate this immediately.
If my reputation is damaged,
the company will sue if need be.
Even if you are innocent,
the employee satisfaction survey
is also an important part
before your appointment.
I hope you prioritize this aspect as well.
What must come will come.
Instead of waiting passively,
why not make the first move?
Did you send the email?
It was not me. I didn't send it.
Not you?
Are you that naive?
Who do you think Luan Nian is?
Do you think some tasteless scandals
can bring him down?
Mr. Lin will soon be transferred
to the US headquarters.
- Do you know that?
- Do I know that?
Last week, at the executives' meeting,
Mr. Lin already submitted
his handover plan,
yet you're still asking me if I know that?
I'm asking you about that email
about Luan Nian.
- Are you a fool?
Once Mr. Lin leaves,
who will take over his position?
Why do you think Luan Nian
spent so much effort
doing the suppliers' database?
He's showing the higher-ups
that he can manage systematically.
So?
When you pull such a big stunt,
they'll still trace it back to me
in the end.
How can I compete for Mr. Lin's position?
It's like putting a knife to my throat
by giving him the perfect weapon.
Du Anni, are you mad,
or do you think I no longer want this?
Fine. Don't worry.
If something happens,
I'll make sure you won't be implicated.
- No way.
- Seriously?
That is crazy.
- Yes.
- There are pictures too.
- It can't be fake.
- Flora.
Flora.
Did you receive the email?
You didn't?
Quick. Come here, quickly.
LIME'S SENIOR EXECUTIVE
FOOLS AROUND WITH MULTIPLE WOMEN
I'M ZHANG XIN, EX-GIRLFRIEND OF LUAN NIAN
LIME'S DIRECTOR IN CHINA
I'm going back first.
Lumi.
I've been looking all over for you.
I just came out for some fresh air.
Even you know about it?
Don't believe in it.
This woman used to harass me too.
She called me from overseas
and investigated my background thoroughly.
She even knows
where my parents are staying.
She also harassed other colleagues
and clients.
She's just crazy.
She also sent videos. Seriously.
Is Luke a fool or what?
Why did he date a woman like this?
Do you have the video? Show me.
I know Luan Nian isn't the violent sort.
But…
His name will never be cleared.
Actually, I was there that day.
You were there? Why?
I wanted to buy Luke a meal to thank him,
so I went there.
Tell me what happened that day.
It's a long story.
Don't tell me.
Tell the investigation unit directly.
I'll go with you.
When this woman harassed me,
I had a grudge with her.
So, I kept a record of her spam calls
and emails.
Let's go and become
Luke's witnesses together.
They are from the headquarters.
They are probably here
because of this incident.
Tracy.
Lisa. Take them to the meeting room first.
- All right.
- This way, please.
Why are you two here?
We want to become Luke's witnesses.
- What witness?
- The email.
Regarding this,
Luke specifically mentioned
that he didn't want anyone else
to get involved.
Tracy, is this serious?
Don't worry.
The company will deal with it properly.
Go back and wait for updates.
Remember.
Don't ever get yourself involved in this.
I'm going to work.
Perhaps Luke does have a plan.
Let's wait and see.
If we can't attest for him,
we can still think of some other ways.
What kind of person
do you think Luan Nian is?
He's strict.
He's a little heartless,
but he is indeed talented.
Strict. Professional. Serious.
A very good leader.
His flaws…
He gets too much attention from women.
Have you seen him
acting overly intimate with others?
I don't think so.
I'm not sure.
Never.
Do you know anything
about Luan Nian's ex-girlfriend?
How would I know about his private life?
No.
Do you think Luan Nian
has a violent tendency?
- No.
- Of course not.
Do the silent treatment
and being controlling count?
I'm not sure.
Let's skip the pleasantries
and go straight to the point.
Tracy mentioned you would like
to clear something up.
It isn't a clarification per se.
Everyone, you can look at this.
This isn't just an email sent to everyone.
SENDING METHOD: BCC
The sender used the BCC function
and added every receiver manually.
What does this mean?
It means two things. One.
The sender knows the internal
staff organization of Lime clearly.
That is why the person
can choose the recipients precisely.
Two. She deliberately avoided using BCC
and hid the list of all recipients
to prevent me from finding
the source of the leak.
But it is also possible that you leaked
this information to your ex-girlfriend.
You are right.
However, among the recipients
of this email,
there are 11 new employees
who joined less than a year ago.
I broke up with my ex-girlfriend
more than a year ago.
She would never get the email addresses
of these new employees.
Is your dad crazy?
We already opened for business, and now
he wants to take back the property.
My dad doesn't allow me to run a bar.
Why didn't he say this earlier?
If the bar closes down,
all the money we invested will be gone.
My savings don't fall from the sky.
Will your dad compensate me?
Why don't you go talk to my father?
Hey, that's your dad.
I… I can't believe dictatorship
still exists at this time and age.
Luan Nian, isn't your father
and his father best buddies?
Go and talk to him.
Can you two think before you speak?
Asking Luan Nian to talk to his father?
Your bar will close down even sooner.
Exactly. What a terrible idea.
His father and my father
are always on the same page.
Exactly.
Enough. Let's not talk about this.
I'm looking for all of you today
because I need a favor.
- What's wrong?
- You didn't invest a single cent.
Of course, you don't care.
I can cover the equipment
and renovation fees of the bar.
Find a quiet place
to reopen the bar later.
Here's your sponsor daddy.
- Oh my!
- Daddy.
- Get lost.
- You're so generous, Daddy.
Hurry up.
It's your turn to help me out now.
- Go to a place with me later.
- Sure.
- We'll do anything for you.
- No problem.
Over there.
The electrical box is over there.
I thought the circuit breaker
had tripped back then.
After I investigated, the wires
were obviously cut by someone else.
I thought it was done by some naughty kid
from the neighborhood.
When the power went out,
my shop's CCTV stopped recording.
Moreover, I watched the video.
I'm sure she already set up
the camera behind this wall
and edited the captured footage.
Looking at the video's angle,
I'm sure she was recording from there.
Yes.
You two have only been together
for a few days,
and she's already working
with outsiders to set you up.
Do you still not get it?
She was used.
Otherwise, she wouldn't have found
a hidden place like mine.
What is this important deal you're in?
Your enemy had to go out of their way
to film the whole thing.
The only benefit of this job
is that I get to stay away from my father.
We don't have to investigate it.
No.
We must find this jerk.
Even if you're quitting,
you still can't take this lying down.
That's right.
Tan, whose car is this?
What car?
It's for delivering goods
for the shop. Why?
This car has a dashcam.
It has always been recording.
It must have recorded the whole thing.
- You're really lucky.
- Come on. Let's go back to the hotel.
- Let's go.
LUAN NIAN'S SUSPENSION NOTICE
After internal discussion,
the general manager's office
at headquarters has decided
that all of Luke Luan's duties
will be suspended from today onward
until the investigation result
is released.
During the suspension,
all of Luke Luan's duties
will be temporarily handled by Alex Zhang.
What kind of person
do you think Luan Nian is?
He is a very good leader.
Although he looks aloof and cold
and unapproachable on the outside,
I find him to be patient
after getting to know him.
Moreover, he keeps personal issues
separate from work.
When he is socializing outside,
he'll make sure
his female colleagues feel safe.
He is willing to share his knowledge
even with those
who are not his subordinates.
Many people in the company, including me,
have received his guidance.
Hello.
Visitor needs to register…
Hello. Welcome home.
‪REMOTE, 10:37 PM
It's the middle of the night.
The neighbors will complain
if you keep pressing
the doorbell like crazy.
Don't you know the passcode for my door?
Come in.
You didn't change the passcode?
Why should I?
Are you all right?
Not really.
My face is ruined.
I'm too embarrassed to see anyone.
Did you…
Did you fight with the people
of the investigation unit?
You are really imaginative.
I got nicked by a razor.
All because you keep pressing
the doorbell.
Do you have a band-aid?
Let me put it on for you.
It's in the coffee table's drawer.
Forget it.
It's nothing serious.
Did the investigation unit
talk to you today?
I came here to tell you
that I can be your witness
if you want.
Aren't you trying
to keep a distance from me?
I know you don't want others
to get involved,
but now is not the time for that.
What do you mean?
You've been suspended.
Have you seen those pictures?
You can look at them.
Other people might not see the difference,
but you should know
that the person isn't me.
Come with me.
Let me take you somewhere.
Where is this?
I want to open a bar in the mountains.
What do you think of this place?
Here?
In the mountains.
Something like a private bar.
It'll only be open to a handful of people.
Do you think it'll work?
This place
is good for stargazing.
All right. This is the place, then.
You're making a decision so casually?
Then, I think this place
could use a little makeover.
I'll take your advice.
This place is indeed good for stargazing.
Are you really leaving Lime?
Is this incident that serious?
I don't lose anything if Lime fires me.
Lime will lose a lot, in fact.
You must never leave Lime.
Don't give up.
Because I think you are a great teacher.
I can learn a lot
from you.
Shang Zhitao.
Isn't your desire for knowledge
too strong?
I…
I don't want to lose the opportunity
to learn from you.
Besides, I don't want
to be eliminated from Lime
because of my incompetence.
You might be harsh when you're teaching,
but
everything you've said has been useful.
If I promise you that I won't leave,
can you not keep your distance
from me tonight?
Why are you staring at me?
Am I more interesting than the stars?
The person who falls
for the other person first
will lower all their guard
and lose everything.
I know this.
But I'm just worried
that this wonderful moment
is a result of my recklessness.
It's too late tonight.
I still have to go to work tomorrow.
Let's go back first.
Sure.
Boss. The image verification result,
the footage that shows the truth,
and information about
all related people are inside.
Do you want to submit it
to the investigation unit
or…
Why didn't you
submit this to the investigation
unit yourself?
No need.
But Alex said he didn't do any of these.
Even if he didn't, he is still implicated.
If you still want
to progress further in your career,
making fewer enemies isn't a bad thing.
Yes.
If this breach of confidence
becomes public,
the consequences will be far more dire
than my scandals.
It is no longer an issue
of an employee's character,
but a breach of confidence
caused by internal in-fighting.
When that happens,
the headquarters will punish us,
and all our peers
in the advertising industry
will see us as a laughingstock.
Clients will even switch
to other companies
because of this.
It's just not worth it.
Once this incident is over,
the position of interim general manager
is yours.
It is
supposed to be yours anyway.
Of course.
"Following a thorough investigation
by the joint investigation team,
it is proven that the allegations against
Lime Advertising China's
Creative Director, Luke Luan,
are false and defamatory."
"Relevant details will not be disclosed
to respect the wishes of the parties.
Moving forward,
Lime China's Legal Department
will assist Luan Nian
in taking legal action against Zhang Xin.
Notice is hereby given."
"After a unanimous decision,
Luan Nian will now be appointed
as Lime Advertising China's
Interim General Manager."
APPOINTMENT NOTICE
Hello, Mr. Luan.
Inform every division
to have a budget meeting in one hour.
Yes.
The empress has returned.
Excuse me. Please wait
for a while, everyone.
I have so much work to do
as soon as I come back?
These documents require the signature
of a general manager.
Go ahead, Mr. Luan.
I've submitted Flora's promotion to SAE.
Please approve it.
When do you plan to move your office?
Mr. Lin's office has been cleared.
I won't be moving.
This floor is nice.
It's convenient for meetings.
No problem. It's your decision.
You just got appointed.
The most important task
is to restructure our sales team.
They are big shots in the industry.
It's not easy to manage them.
I've been thinking about a reformation.
I'll keep you in the loop
once I come out with the proposal.
Okay. But the elimination rate of the team
should still be kept at 30%.
Otherwise, when the time comes
to evaluate you,
don't blame me
for giving you a bad rating.
Come in.
Luke. Today we need to align the budget
for the project proposal meeting.
I've sent all the details to your email.
Okay.
Who will be present in the meeting?
Since you're newly appointed,
let's visit every division.
Let's go.
Next group.
Let's first talk about the industry
seminar your division is in charge of.
This year, we've decided on cities like
Beijing, Shanghai, Guangzhou, Shenzhen,
Hong Kong, China, Chongqing, and Xiamen.
We also want to invite clients
from various industries
for a joint seminar.
The objective
is client relationship management.
This is also
Lime's most valued annual tradition.
If it's just to maintain
a relationship with clients,
taking them out for a meal and drinks
would be good enough.
A 500,000-yuan budget is good enough.
Why should I spend 17 million yuan
to achieve something
that can be done with 500,000 yuan?
How do you plan to adjust it?
Unless you have a concrete idea,
my suggestion is to remove it completely.
Mr. Luan, what about this?
I'll go back and study more
about this project with my team.
Actually, managing client relationships
is just a small part of this project.
Making an impact in the industry
is also very important.
Besides the list of clients,
what kind of experts can you invite,
and how many potential clients
can you bring?
Study it carefully
before we decide if we want it.
Alex, is that okay with you?
Of course.
What about you, Annie?
Whatever you say.
All right.
I'll have to trouble all of you
to revise everything.
Every budget
will be discussed again tomorrow.
My request is simple.
Think it through
before you decide on doing something.
Once everyone agrees on the core progress,
make sure to report back.
There must be a solution
to every problem you encounter.
Okay?
Mr. Luan is asking
if all of you are okay with it.
- Who is doing the meeting minutes?
- I am.
After the meeting,
send it to everyone
who is in this meeting and CC me.
Okay.
He sure makes full use
of his first day of work.
Be careful. Mind your attitude.
We are talking about more than
10 million yuan. How should I react?
Everyone, gather around.
I have an announcement to make.
There'll be a friendly
basketball match with Yueteng.
It won't be considered as your KPI
or your job.
Which division can handle it?
Who wants to take charge?
I can do it.
Okay.
I'll leave it to you. Thank you.
Feeling vindicated?
Do you feel vindicated?
Yes.
Actually, I received
Luke's email last night.
He told me he would initiate
the project budget meeting
and the project evaluation today.
I got it immediately.
I was sure that he solved everything.
But this morning,
I still felt excited
when I received this email.
It felt so good.
Lumi, what project evaluation?
Can I join?
Because I want to become
an independent project manager.
Doing this helps gather experience.
No, Shang Zhitao.
Are you even normal?
Why do you like to work so much?
If you want to do it,
go and ask the boss directly.
He is now the general manager.
General manager.
Go for it.
Lumi.
You are so capable,
and you can do everything well.
Why don't you request
to handle a project all by yourself?
Handling a project all by myself?
Forget it. I'm already tired enough.
I'm working because I just
want something to do.
I have Luke to cover me.
I'm grateful to the competitive Luke
for letting me achieve great things
by doing nothing.
He is quite a hard worker.
If he doesn't work hard,
how can he manage such a big team
in the advertising industry?
Everything is good about him,
but you must never fall for him.
Why not?
He has a really bad temper.
Even someone as experienced as me
will probably be brokenhearted
and shed tears because of him.
However, I don't mind being friends
with someone as handsome as him.
Tracy, you're right.
You run your mouth like a train.
I'm the high-speed rail.